

Work Experience

UX/UI designer at Helfer (Freelance)

2021 - 2022

- conception, sketching and design of the web apps;
- full remote work in a team with 3 developers;
- presentation to the client and potential users.

Web Project Manager at Smile (www.smile.fr)

2018 - now

- defining client's needs, briefing teams, creating specifications;
- presentations and facilitating workshops for clients;
- delivering massive evolutions and complete site rework from A to Z (UX research and conception till development and tests on production);
- coordination of remote teams : UX/UI designers, developers, QA, DevOps;
- management of more than 7 projects simultaneously;
- resolving blocking issues and crisis situations, conflict management;
- regular reporting and assuring KPI realization defined for each client.

Front-end developer - UX designer at Alteca

May - Oct 2018

- (www.alteca.fr/fr/) Internship
- making layouts and prototypes in Sketch & Marvel; - front-end development in Angular 4, 5, LESS / SASS;
- API REST consumption.

Business Developer at RGAND (B2B, HORECA)

2016 - 2017

- benchmark analysis;
- product presentation (web apps) to potential partners;
- formatting advertising banners on the Web.

Team leader at Sokhnut-Ukraine

2015 - 2018

- making educational workshops for children 4-16 years;
- organization and coordination of events of various themes and scales (up to 300 people);
- creation and managing of youth projects;
- leading groups of 40+ people on educational trips to Israel;
- formatting advertising for social networks and advertising mails.

Education

DesignLab Course

2021

UI for UX designers

UX Design Institute, Ireland

2020 - 2021

Professional diploma in UX design

Université Lumiére Lyon 2, France

2016 - 2018

M2: Informatics of decisions and statistics for management

Kharkiv National University of Economics, Ukraine

2012 - 2018

M2, BAC+4: Management of international affairs, with mention

Profile

Double experience in Design and Project Management; Double master degree; 4 languages; 5 YEARS OF EXPERIENCE in IT

Contact

Portfolio

annakhokhlova.fr

LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/anna-khokhlova

Email

annette.khokhlova@gmail.com

Phone

+33 6 20 47 87 15

Address

Cagnes-sur-Mer, France

Skills

Hard Skills

Wireframing, Prototyping, User Research, Affinity mapping, Workshop facilitation, Project management

Soft Skills

Effective communication, Leadership, Problem solving, Stakeholder management

Tools

Figma, Sketch, Marvel, Invision, Adobe Suite, NinjaMock, Balsamiq, Axure, HTML/CSS, Bootstrap, Drupal; basic mastery of JavaScript, jQuery, Angular2+, SASS/SCSS, Grid

Languages

French, English, Ukrainian, russian